Well, done some work on the offensive
line. Um, you just how do you feel about
what what you guys have been able to do
here with these two waves of free
agency?
>> Good so far. Obviously, still a lot of
work to be done. Uh, I think, you know,
as we look specifically with that
offensive line group, um, good players,
but also very versatile. Uh, and
particularly like with Elton and and
Titus, you know, both of those guys are
players who can, you know, play at a
quality starting level.
um at multiple positions across the
offensive line and that's super helpful
because it really is a war of attrition
with that position group. I think
something like we looked at it as either
23 or 24 teams last year played less
than 50% with their starting five. Um of
course we were we were one of them. And
so to have that resiliency built into a
position group where you have guys that
can start all across the line of
scrimmage, it's it's really important in
addition to the flexibility it gives you
going into the draft. So, where are you
playing Elton Jenkins?
>> Yeah, so it's uh it's TBD. He's honestly
like um you know, he can play center, he
can play guard. Um that's something that
we're going to sort out as we get us a
little bit further through the
acquisition season. Um I mean, this is a
guy who's played, you know, starting
level stabs at left tackle, right
tackle, left guard, center. Um you know,
he can really do it all. We would view
him more as an interior player. that is
what we think is is is more his natural
home, whether it's center, whether it's
guard, you know, we'll work through that
as we put together a position early into
spring.
>> Is as you talk about that versatility
piece, how how important is that going
to be for how you guys approach
potentially drafting looking at
alignment in the in the draft?
>> Yeah, it it just it gives flexibility.
That's probably the the biggest thing.
like, you know, we we feel good if we
had to line up and play today that we
could, you know, with the with that
group of linemen, but it certainly uh
doesn't pigeon hole you into anything as
you get to draft league.
>> But who would be your center today?
>> Today, hard to say. Like honestly, it
really depends on the competition at um
you at really one of the other guard
spots opposite uh Zion. Um, obviously we
have Elton, we resigned Tevin, you know,
Zack and and Luke, they're guys that are
going to have greater opportunity now
that those bets are gone. So, it's
really we would just be looking for the
best pair of pair.
>> Yeah, finish that thought. So, Zack
finished playing center. Is he earmarked
competed center?
>> You mean uh L? Do you mean Luke? Zack.
Zack. Zach really finished playing guard
for us. You mean Luke finished playing
center for a Posick?
>> Well, Luke got hurt in the in the Cincy
game and Zack finished uh
>> center. Zach's more natural position is
guard. He can do he can do both
competitor for I would say this. Well,
he can do both. We think his more
natural position is a guard. Is that is
that fair enough to say? Yeah.
>> Andrew, since this was such a hot hot
topic over the last few days or so, can
you address um what was the impetus
behind the Miles Garrett contract
modifications and then also of course
the correlary to that is everybody
thinks you're going to trade them. So,
if you could talk about those two
issues.
>> Yeah. So, I think you guys know like
standard practice. I don't comment on
player contracts. I guess probably the
easiest thing to say is if you know if
we wanted to trade miles, we wouldn't
have need to make a contract adjustment.
So, it does have anything to do with
that.
>> Why did you do it?
>> So, again, I don't comment on player
contracts. I understand I understand the
question in the interest, but um it's
just something that we've always felt
not to comment on player contracts or
contract management strategy.
>> But, so can you state unequivocally that
you're not treating Miles Garrett? I'd
say this, Mary Kay, Miles is a career
Brown. He is one of the faces of our
organization. I think we've been very
clear both past and present in terms of
our feelings. So, I I I understand all
the questions. I'll be honest, I don't
really want to waste a ton more breath
on the topic.
>> Sure.
>> But you feel like you guys are in a good
spot with Miles?
>> We do.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. as it pertains to the quarterback
position. Um, is it just safe to assume
that the incumbents the current room
will be competing for the starting
position or when you look to add a
potential fourth quarterback, would you
prefer the draft? Would you prefer
signing a vet for agency or how you kind
of looking at the quarterback room at
the stands?
>> Yeah, I'd say Daniel that you know, you
always want to be flexible because you
don't know how circumstances change or
what opportunities come your way. Um,
our lean would be if we do add someone
to the quarterback room, you know, it
would be someone who's a who's a younger
player most likely. Um, but I can't
state that definitively because I don't
I don't know what the next couple weeks
will hold. Um, anyone that we bring in
at any spot on the roster, you know, our
thought is that they are compet
competing to play. um they have
something that that we like in their
skill set and um our expectation would
be for them to work hard it
with regards to the Shadore versus
Deshawn specifically. How much do you
balance short-term with long-term
knowing that
team control with Shidor goes well
beyond Yep. 26 whereas Deshawn there is
sort of our you know another hurdle that
create.
>> Yeah. I think we're probably just more
focused on performance but in and in and
best player certainly time horizon
factors into that. um you know, but just
of any veteran player, there's there's
no rule against extending the players
contract if they if they perform and
they do well. So, I wouldn't necessarily
box it into any, you know, one uh
approach. It it really will be
performance based.
>> Andrew, I understand how do you value
Miles? Everyone knows he's the best
player in the league, but you have the
team to serve it to you. So, why don't
you think you could get out of this hole
by using your greatest asset?
Collect picks. Yeah. Which we'll always
do what we think is in the best interest
of the organization. Um, we really like
our core and I think as we look at the
team, you know, we have an elite young
defense. Uh, we have a really, you know,
rebuilt allins line. We have what, nine
picks this upcoming draft and I think
seven are in the top 150. Um, you know,
three in the top 40. Um, we have a good
offensive young core that we we brought
in last year. Um, and honestly, like as
we saw last year, there there are more
than one way to generate assets at FL.
So, um, we'll always do what's best for
the organization. Uh, but we feel really
good to put a roster right to to the
draft. at the combat. Uh you kind of
were 5050. I mean it like it almost
seemed like Deshawn and Shador like you
were totally fine with either one of
them if it worked out that one of them
were the start. Is that still where you
stand right now? Is does it sort of
still seem like they each have an equal
opportunity to win the starting job?
>> Yeah, I'd say as we sit here on, you
know, March 29th and nobody has touched
the grass, nobody has really worked with
our coaching staff, uh like I wouldn't
handicap it for anyone. Um, I think they
all everyone in that room deserves
opportunity and so we'll we'll certainly
know a lot more as we get through the
spring. We'll know even more as we get
to camp. Uh, but I think you know
honestly we wouldn't be we wouldn't be
doing the right thing for the team. We
wouldn't be doing the right thing for
that position if um, you know, if we
didn't go in with it eyes wide open.
>> What was the impetus to um, expanding
the the scope on draft on trading draft
picks? um you know did you see the
reaction to it and do you expect it to
pass?
>> Yeah. So Daniel in terms of the impetus
we've largely been believers in
um I guess easing restrictions in terms
of how teams can use their their
resources. So this is like in a similar
vein um and really just getting getting
I guess giving more flexibility to teams
in terms of uh volume and creativity of
transactions. Um yeah, as we look at it,
uh our league relative to the other
major leagues, uh you know, the
basketball you can trade, um you'll pick
seven years out. Cocky, I don't think
there's any limitation. Obviously,
baseball is the most restricted, but you
can't you can't trade picks at all. Um
to us, three years is really probably
more of like an arbitrary uh you know,
marker in terms of like how far out you
can you know, deploy your future assets.
Um, honestly like Daniel, I think like a
lot of the,
you know, perhaps resistance is this
idea that, you know, a a desperate
general manager, a desperate desperate
head coach could, you know, leverage a
team's, you know, future irresponsibly.
You know, I think that's a little bit
more rooted in fear than reality though.
I think for two reasons. I think number
one, um, there is always cornership
oversight for every every franchise. But
two, probably the bigger point, like if
you look back over the last 10 years, I
think there have been 27 trades that
have included a pick three years out.
And of those 27, only only three have
included a firstrounder and only another
four have included even day two pick. So
like I don't think you're all of a
sudden going to see this trend where
people are trading picks, you know, four
or five years out. I think those are
very rare circumstances. But what it
does do is it gives you more creative
alternatives for I would say maybe less
signature or less um aggressive moves uh
because of how you want to balance the
discounting of present versus future
assets. Is there a rigid rule now? There
seem to be confusion. Is it an NFL rule
you can only trade in three years out?
Is it more of an under?
>> No.
>> Yeah, that's a
>> So if you were the the receiving GM of a
trade, how do you devalue a pick three
years in advance?
>> Yeah. So number one
>> Yeah.
It's a great question to so
traditionally I say let me back up every
team probably has their own methodology
probably the
you know traditional discounting is like
you discount it or discount it around
now there there will be varying opinions
of if that's like an effective uh you
know valuation of future picks but I
think that's what actually creates some
unique transactional opportunities
because teams will value present versus
future picks much much differently. It
just gives you more opportunities for
creative solutions that benefit both
sides.
>> And when you talk about um the
quarterback situation, how realistic is
it that you will add somebody? You said
it would probably be a younger guy. How
realistic is it that you would add
somebody that would actually come in
here and compete for the starting job
and then the correlary to that is just
how uh realistic is it that you would
draft Tai Simpson at some point?
>> Yeah. So I I guess I'll start with the
first question. I think it's wholly
realistic uh you know Mary Kay um in
terms of them competing for their
starting job. Anyone we bring in we want
we want to compete but a large part of
that will be for any young player will
depend on their acclamation to the NFL
and their readiness to to play and
that's really done on a case by case uh
basis. Um in terms of Tai specifically
um I think you can understand we
wouldn't necessarily come in on specific
prospects.
um have spent time with Tai. I think
that's you know that's obvious and will
continue to do so. Uh but I think he has
a bright NFL future.
>> Last year you were very visible at the
quarterback proday zinc. This year
you're not. Why?
>> I think just every year you see Tony um
uh those warrior picking the particular
class the access that you have
particular individuals. But we also do
have uh uh one of them mubbed out for
the draft. So there still is a lot of
work to do. Prote are done.
>> Yep. That is for Indiana's. Yeah.
>> So Tony, I think actually like last year
most of our trips were actually privates
as opposed to the prodays. Uh so I
wouldn't say that's the only touch point
is you went to the pro days and then you
stayed over or the visits. So that's
actually not true. That's not Yeah.
Yeah. We were at the
>> Travis Hunters and the Shadors. That was
the only one.
>> Oh, I'll be back.
>> Uh obviously still no official answer
from Joel in terms of what his decision
is going to be. Do you guys feel you
kind of have to operate from a place of
where you're not you can't be you can't
bank on him coming back? Yes, sister.
>> Yeah, I think that's I think that's
fair. Um, you know, Joel's going to take
the time that he needs to, you know,
make the decision for the next step in
in his career and like he should, right?
It's a it's a pretty big life decision
for him. Um I don't think that we can
operate under the assumption that uh
he's absolutely coming back because he
hasn't said that space and um and I do
think that there's a little bit of like
a you know in a definite time period in
terms of where he's going to make that
decision because it is it's a major one
for a person and we respect that and
appreciate it but
>> but is the door open like do you still
want him back given you know you guys
obviously let the money the dead money
kind of accelerate on your cap this year
So, you know, and there might have been
a way you could have somewhere maybe
maneuvered that if you if you could have
done it differently. So, is is it still
like the open door for him to deter?
>> Yeah, I'd say there's the door is always
open for for good players. Certainly,
uh, you know, players who have done as
much as what that Joel has for the
organization, but you know, ultimately
it's it's his decision in terms of how
he wants to navigate things before.
>> You hold pick six and externally
everybody's guessing on two to five. Are
you guys guessing too?
You mean uh like who who am I who who's
going at you? Yeah. So, uh as we get
into April, Zach, we'll do a lot of um
scenario planning and we'll we'll get
into those we'll get into those
exercises. I'd say right now we're still
more towards the end of the evaluation
phase, you know, especially as like the
prodays die down, the privates die down,
uh you know, a little bit of like
touch-up film, but you know, here over
the next month, we'll we'll get into
that more heavily.
>> Who makes the call quarterback? Is it an
organizational decision or is that
Todd's call strictly
>> in terms of start? Uh that's always
that's always been the head coach's
decision. Yeah. Whoever whoever is
playing on the field, that's always the
head coach's Yeah.
>> Andrew, what's going on at wide
receivers so far? You just added a
return specialist.
>> Yeah. I I'd say that we have a group of
individuals that uh that we like
internally uh that we're excited to see
as they come back into the offseason
program. Um, you know, I would imagine
that at some point be off seasonason,
we'll add some external talent, but like
I said, we're March 29th. We've got
probably another five months in the
heaviest period of the acquisition
season. So, we'll see where it goes.
>> How aggressively did you pursue veteran
wide receivers and even even veteran
quarterbacks and maybe why or why not
did you why or why not did you pursue it
aggressively?
>> You know, I I would not necessarily go
into those details, Daniel, although I
understand the interest. Um, I'd say
this, you know, our focus primarily was
on the offensive line, obviously, um,
going into pre- agency, um, while still
maintaining an opportunistic mindset at
some of the other spots. Um, I think
the, you know, the great thing about the
NFL is you have a number of different,
you know, spots you could turn on in
terms of, you know, player acquisition,
whether it's the draw off, whether it's
free agency, whether it's the trade
market.
So it's about poor of those lovers of
the red
>> specifically about Shador. Well, you
have mentioned at the end of the season
K has mentioned that he still has a long
way to go.
>> How far does he have to go to get to the
point where you guys would feel
comfortable putting, you know, to see
his hands right from the start?
>> Yeah, I I think that's a little bit TBD,
Mary Kay, because I think all of our
guys coming in, they're going to learn a
new offensive system. you know, we're
gonna have a fair amount of of turnover
on that side of the ball. They'll have
new teammates to learn, you know, which
is why the spring will be really
important um you for the guys that are
at the offseason program for us to
really really get a sense of their their
progress year over year. But, you know,
he's been working really hard. Um you
know, I would expect him to take us up
forward and, you know, we'll we'll deal
with that kind of week by week in five
month.
>> You said uh you prefer a younger fourth
quarterback. Does that mean draft pick
only or a younger veteran? I I wouldn't
say I would not uh I wouldn't rule out
any method of acquisition.
>> Yeah. What What would an 18th game being
added into your job and how would you
view
>> that? I I'll be honest. I don't think it
would have a huge difference other than
um like I'd probably be most curious how
injury injury rates change more than
anything. like I could see a world where
at certain positions maybe it changes
your approach for your depth. Um that
I'd also imagine that that 18th game
would come with some type of trade-off
whether it's a by-week or less you know
less preseason games or things like
that. But in terms of I guess maybe the
fundamental aspects of roster building,
I don't think it would have a major
impact.
>> So along those lines, but I'll figure
out how I want to ask this kind of open.
You guys have had to play 12
quarterbacks in three years
>> leaguewide. I think it was 62 last year
and 59 the year before that. That's it's
a wild number. Is Is that inevitable? Is
that something that can be fixed? Like
just what kind of what's your thoughts
on all those quarterbacks playing? Does
it change your plan? Does it have to
change your plan?
>> No, I I I'd say this. I think probably
there's you could put it in two
different buckets like durability versus
performance at that position. Um, and
part of it is like if you're if you're
turning over, you're probably going to
have a little bit more uh
opportunity or at least more like not
even just relative to quarterbacks. Uh,
I do think the durability component is
is real because that's a very physically
and mentally demanding position in our
sport, especially as like, you know,
Dlinemen become that much bigger, that
much faster, that much uh, you know,
that much stronger. And um it's a big
release reason that we believed in in
carrying three because it is a very long
season. Um and I don't I don't see that
part changing anytime soon.
>> Coming off about the durability, but so
the offensive line more specifically
when you kind of gone back and looked at
the last three years. I mean the number
of I mean it's it has that have you
adjusted anything based off of kind of
re-examining the last few years the
injuries what what has kind of led to it
and and you know kind of what have you
guys learned from you know studying the
the amount of turnover you guys have had
on the line.
>> Yeah. So, I think number one, it's um
it's fairly prevalent across the league.
Like probably keeping a position group
of five players all on the field the
whole season is probably fairly
unrealistic. That's one thing that we've
learned. Um two, I think if you look at
where we were, take out the 25 season,
the 24 23 in terms of our injury rates,
um it's a big reason that we made some
of the changes that we did in the health
and performance basis. And um we really
started to see those returns, you know,
this year in terms of keeping those guys
on the field. Um to that group
specifically, I think probably this this
past year, you know, really a big part
of it was, you know, that group really
did age out for us and we understood
that we were going in with a little bit
of an older group there.
I do think that uh as we turn over that
room um I think or hope that some of
that will take care of itself in
addition to some of the changes that
we've made in in uh downstairs in the
healthy performance spaces.
>> Just following up real quick just but
you sort of look at like the wans was a
flu you know seeing a lot of them as
kind of flukeish the the way they
happen. I think it No, I think it's a
combination of both. Like I think it's a
combination of uh you know guys who you
understand like you're going to have
guys on your roster that have some type
of medical history. Like you're not
going to build a team of of
unfortunately all durable guys. Some
certainly are flukes um in the sense of
hey is it a contact injury? Does someone
get thrown to somebody's you know knees
or legs? Um, and some of it, some of it
may be like, hey, guys, their injury
risk does change as their career
progress, whether it's because of their
age or it's because of previous
injuries. So, I'd like to sit here and
say it's like, hey, one, it's just one
thing and then it's an easy cure all.
But, um, you know, I think that would be
unfair to say. A year ago, it was it was
at the owner meetings where the the
trade from 2 to 5 really kind of started
to to come about, um, with James
Gladstone. um a year later, how do you
reflect on um that trade, maybe what you
got, you know, from the rookies in the
short term and also like the long-term
outlook as well as, you know, how the
trade has kind of set you up for this
this upcoming draft?
>> Yeah, I think um it's something that
made sense for both organizations at the
time. Um, I think for us, you know, the
ability to, you know, realistically
draft Mason, draft Q, um, and then
obviously be sitting here with with a
pick 24. Um, it made sense for
where we are in our team's life cycle.
Um, and it's a way, you know, maybe a
little bit to Tony's question earlier
that you're able to manufacture assets
or resources without necessarily, you
know, trading away a veteran a veteran
player. Um, so it was an opportunity
that that that came about and we were
fortunate for what we were trying to
achieve. Um, and we do think that it
puts us in a good position with what
we've also added already this year.
>> Knoxville teams are reluctant to give up
27 picks this year
>> because of the quality. I wouldn't say
so cuz I think uh
so I want to think like what is it six
teams have
two first this year and or you know
something along those lines. I can't I
can't remember how many have given up uh
have given up uh their 27 picks but I I
think there will be a market for those
27 picks if I had to guess.
>> And do you want to be in that mark?
>> Hey listen we can have more you know
premium assets. It's it's helpful. I
think you can look back to last year
like, you know, there are some really
good players in in last year's draft,
the top of last year's draft, we felt
like we got one of them at last year's
draft and by moving back three spots
essentially to get a one and a two would
make made sense for you.
>> In a perfect world, would you trade down
from number six in this draft? And uh
then I I have a followup.
>> I I think it really just depends on the
prospects that are available. Um,
yeah, I I'd like to I look, this is why
I say I don't know that I don't know
that I tell you guys this is I don't
know that we are going to be picking six
at the end of April. Uh, and if we are
picking six, I have no idea where we're
going to take it this spring. And so,
um, we try and remain flexible, you
know, as we go into draft weekend. And
we want to use the asset in the best way
possible. Whether that's sitting and
picking, trading up, trading down,
trading up for a veteran player. I know
I said this last year and people thought
it was just it was just GM talk, but it
really is the truth.
>> And the follow never do just GM.
>> The the followup to that is uh do you
think there is a world in which you can
secure another first round pick for next
year?
>> I'm sure that world exists. I you know I
I can't I don't I don't know the
specifics of it today.
>> So far you've only had one offensive
lineman pay a visit to Berea reportedly.
>> I'd say so I'd say this Tony I would not
uh
can't believe everything you read. So,
yeah. Well, I think we've had we
actually had a lot. So, a lot of
offense, but
>> can you tell us who some of the other
ones?
>> I'd prefer not to.
>> Are you guys motor and the league though
or each other's presets?
>> No, that's not. So, you you have to
report it to like uh uh the local.com.
>> But no, it's not like it's not like you
can see who every team's 30s are. No.
Yeah. Last year you guys did a lot of
dinners here. Does this off private
workouts? Is it more in your building
this year with with the draft prospects?
>> I wouldn't say that's necessarily the
case. Like the volume's down a little
bit. Um, but we still had we still had
our fair share.
>> Off of Daniel kind of mentioned the
trade last year sort of starting maybe
at this time of year.
>> Would you say this year it's less likely
that that comes to fruition before draft
weekend like the way it did last year
just because of the nature of where you
guys are versus where you were drafted
last year?
>> That's a great question. I wouldn't say
that's ne it's it's it's a it's a very
reasonable uh conclusion. Uh but I
wouldn't I wouldn't say that that's
necessarily the case.
>> How does the how does the multitude of
teams that have multiple first round
picks obviously including yourselves.
How does that kind of like change the
dynamic of the first round? Maybe
flexibility with trades and how you kind
of prepare and maneuver.
>> I actually don't think it changes it
that much. you know, Daniel, uh,
maybe I'll be gone once we get to draft
weekend, but I I don't I don't think
that's really had a major impact.
>> So, you don't think that it'd be easier
or harder to shoot cuz at all?
>> I don't really when you're looking at
these quarterbacks in this draft, you
know, there seems to be a lot of,
you know, Tai not enough, you know, not
a lot of reps in terms of scheme start
nerds
of health and and that, you know, how
much did that impact? How much I mean
when you're evaluating these guys, how
much how much are you weighing those
kind of extra extra things?
>> Context is important for any prospect
and that's not just the quarterback
position, but probably uh particularly
strong for the QB position because it's
so interdependent on everything else,
you know, around it. Um so those
absolutely you know weigh into
uh both the evaluation and then the
final valuation in terms of okay where
do you value the particular prospect so
some we absolutely take out of account
>> most gyms don't go to prodays like you
why don't you go basically what's your
philosophy on that
>> yeah I'd say that
>> like Ohio State
>> yeah so I'd say um number one every
every GM probably has their own process
um number two as a general manager
you're you're not the personnel
director, you're you're overseeing the
entire football operation. That's
certainly a part of it. Probably the
bigger thing is like I'd say a lot of us
that maybe don't hit the proday circuit
go out a lot in the fall um and see
these guys. Like for me, the biggest
part of the per day is if you haven't
seen a guy, let's say move around live
or let's say it's a prospect that you're
going to have play in another role or
another position, maybe you get to see
that in the workout. But for someone
that you've seen multiple times in the
fall, you've seen them live and they're
you've seen them at the combine, you
know, work out. Um the question is like,
okay, you only have so much time. How
additive can that actually be? And then
the other thing is they're always all on
film as well. So you know, every proday
that's out there, you get you get on
film. What about talking to trainers and
equipment and we
>> So you should be doing that fall. Okay.
You do do that. You do that should be
doing that fall. When you talk about
rebuilding and the cycle of your roster,
what can fans expect in terms of your
ability to contend for the playoffs this
year?
>> Yeah, I think we're way too early for
that discussion because we are two weeks
into the new league year. So, we've got
a long way to go until um you know, we
complete the roster before week one. So,
that really will be the focus and then
we can talk about that once we get to
>> So, you mentioned you you could consider
Jenkins a setter or Kurt
So, who's your left tackle? I mean,
other than Dwan Johnson, you don't have
an alternative.
>> Yeah. Uh, I'd say, you know, between
Dewan, you know, Titus has obviously
played there before was left tackle as
well. Um, we've had KT.
So, we do have options there. Tony,
>> is it Dwan an option so I could
potentially even side or do you view
him?
>> No. Strictly as a tackle. Yeah. And are
you still reasonably sure or completely
100% sure that Quinn Sean, I know he'll
be ready for the season, but will he be
100% ready for training camp or or where
does that
>> Yeah, he's he's progressing really
really nicely. I'd imagine that we're
going to see him u in some form or
fashion this this spring. Uh and you
know, knock wood, you know, he should be
full curve for camp.
>> Is is his case closed with Hik. Sorry.
Is his case closed with the league? Is
there still any thought of a potential?
Nope.
>> We have no issues. before uh Dewan got
hurt lof back to right tackle. Is that a
no?
>> Nope. Not necessarily. Yeah.
>> Do you agree with the consensus on this
wide rece?
And I guess off of that, how does that
kind of impact how you approach that
position where maybe you don't feel like
you have to, you know, force the issues
super early if if you think you can get
value rated?
>> Well, I think you know that I don't
believe in drafting for E period. Uh
yeah, I don't like probably the best
example last year is like I don't know
that many people had us pegged to take
Carson with the 33rd pick, but that
worked out pretty well for us. Um so
that like regardless of how deep or
shallow it is, that really doesn't play
a huge role into our thinking.
>> I think you know we're going to
>> the quarterback that the Deshawn
contract hasn't gone to where you guys
thought that it would. With one year
left, there's obviously a lot of strong
emotions tied to Deshawn buying the fan
base. What is the benefit to going
through this all over?
>> Yeah, I'd say for us the biggest thing
that I mentioned a little bit earlier,
you know, our charge is to put the best
team on the field and ultimately it
comes down to performance.
Any player that we have on the roster,
we expect to compete. That's what open
to look for.
>> It seems like this draft class of
tackles,
there's a lot of right tackles, it and
you know, the number of true left
tackles, it seems to to vary. Do you
believe that or I know you believe you
know a tackle is is a tackle in a lot of
ways but do do you feel like there's the
depth of true left tackles is is
shallower maybe than
>> I don't and I think uh the distinction
between right and left tackles in
today's game uh like the job
descriptions are they're identical you
know it's not like uh 25 years ago where
you had an openside rusher or a closed
side rusher you had right-handed
formations
I mean, think about how we use Miles,
right? Like, I don't know that uh, hey,
if you're the if you're the left tackle,
you're getting Miles Garrett match him
all the time. The right tap got to be
able to block him, too. Uh, so I just
think those lines have blurred pretty
significantly. Uh, you know, in modern
day football. Um, and you think about
you have Tristan Worse who went from the
right side to the left side. You hear
Detroit talking about moving Su from the
right side to the left side. You know,
Tyron Smith was a career right tackle in
college in high school, moved to the
left side. Um, and then the other way,
you have plenty of left tackles. Jack
Con was a left tackle in college and and
and moved to the right side. So, I I
just think those distinctions are are
are uh a little bit outdated.
>> So, you think that you could get uh a
starting caliber wide receiver or a left
tackle at 24?
>> We'll see. We're not far enough along in
our evaluations to say anything.
>> Martin Emerson, your thoughts?
>> Yeah, love MJ. absolutely love MJ both
as a person and as a player. Um
selfishly would love to have him back. I
think we're also realistic that you know
with MJ and the injury that he's coming
off of, he
to reach his, you know, personal goals,
he's also got to be in a position where
um
he has maybe a strong opportunity to
compete for a starting spot. That's
probably a little bit harder with how
we're configured with Denzel and and and
Tyson, but certainly if that changes in
terms of press, we'd love to back.
>> In the same vein that everyone wants to
speculate that you guys might trade
Miles, I see the same thing for Denzel
everywhere. And I'm guessing that falls
into the same bucket that he's one of
your core players and he's not going in.
>> Yeah, I mean, we'll always do what's
best for the organization. Uh but we're
generally in the business of keeping
elite players as opposed to shima. I
know the um the NFL came out with it
leap guardian that that leafed and I
think for the first time they had GM
grades and no like you personally got to
see I was curious that's old that you
saw you looked at was that like
discussed how do you it is now that's
how seems to me
>> I'm just curious like how do you kind of
like I don't know what the criteria was
but I don't either I guess I guess so
when it comes to I guess you know uh
player satisfaction and these like the
relationship like how do you kind of go
about fostering that and making sure
that you know you're on good terms
you're pretty uh good about developing
daily and uh uh daily interpersonal
interaction with our players. So that's
not something that I would ever need to
see or whatever or wicker report card. I
know a lot's been been written about
that, but we feel good about our guys.
>> Has the uh organization chart changed
with the Podesta leaving? So does the
head coach report to you or the owner?
>> Uh so head coach reports into general
manager. Uh so that is that change. I I
guess I mean it's not something that we
really only spend a lot of time think
about. Tony, we work to get it. Yeah.
>> How about can you just comment on how
the job that Todd has done so far? How
are you guys working together? What do
you think of the staff that he's built?
And and what are you seeing just
>> Todd's awesome like I think you guys
have experienced it with um your
interactions with him. He's really
smart. He's authentic. He's hired an
excellent staff.
>> He's great to work with. And I think
we're both really excited um to get
going on April April 7th when we get
back. But um I I feel very very strongly
that as you all are fans continue to to
see him work in an interaction with him
that uh he will very much endear himself
to this fan base.
>> Good. But how beneficial is it that you
can start those workouts two weeks
earlier? um more the guys coming back in
the cup seat, it's still just voluntary
workouts, but being able to have guys
back to the building with this coach and
staff,
>> it's it's really helpful, Kelsey. And
it's it's a little bit of a crunch, you
know, beforehand because you're like,
"Oh man, the offseason is coming
quickly, but then once you get into it,
one, there's a natural excitement when
the guys come back in the building. Two,
the extra time that they get, you know,
familiar familiarizing themselves with
the with the new staff,
you know, it's excellent. So it's it's
it's an opportunity that we do not take
lightly.
>> Will Miles participate, do you know, in
the OS Stephen program this year?
>> It's a voluntary program. So like I I I
mean I'd imagine he'd do his same
schedule that type of thing.